especially from world of trading places programs very simple incredibly complex
特别是来自交易场所的程序非常简单，非常复杂
and everything in between in this video breakdown or framework
以及此视频细分或框架中的所有内容
for research and development trading algorithms this score
用于研发交易算法的这个分数
workstation producers should gain output input in the case of trading
工作站生产商应在交易的情况下获得输出投入
algorithms in pool financial data and execute trades on the certificate
合并财务数据中的算法并执行证书交易
the commentator of the affiliate strategy
联盟策略的评论者
director communications especially for retail trading sources of three days are
主任沟通，尤其是三天零售交易来源的沟通是
what is usually uni private limited pool quality data quality data can be very
通常什么是uni私人有限池质量数据质量数据可能非常
very expensive recommended if you're just starting out chambre christelle
如果您刚开始使用christelle，则建议非常昂贵
data sheet trade treaty override trading platform sex is a user data
数据表贸易条约否决交易平台性别是用户数据
for free and mortlake computer generated profit
免费和抵押计算机产生的利润
with a lot of interesting facts angie invest in major us equities spd birgit benchmark
有很多有趣的事实，安吉投资了美国主要股票SPD Birgit基准
etf with the single level of risk fsv manager return of ten present because
etf的单级风险fsv经理返现为10，因为
diego managers return of 5% of the same period jugo manager generated whether fit
迭戈经理产生的5％的同期回报迭戈经理产生的是否合适
or significantly different and sp3 and technical systems made of risk for
或明显不同，并且sp3和技术系统存在以下风险
simple invest in spd or bee bachelor investment because you go this examples of
简单地投资于SPD或蜜蜂学士投资，因为您可以通过以下示例
the excess return alpha is generate
产生超额收益阿尔法
alphabetized research processing of service marks of and image completely by
对的服务标记和图像按字母顺序进行完全由
otto access data storage strategies all in one place in my opinion socgen all in
我认为otto访问数据存储策略全都集中在一个地方
one platform is at vdi it is and best way to people to get into
vdi是一个平台，这是人们进入的最佳途径
algorithmic trading research platform suck from copies and cross connect sadly
算法交易研究平台从副本中吸取并交叉连接
account qian recently stop supporting live trading could use them for
钱先生的帐户最近停止支持实时交易，可以将其用于
trading that was ruby ​​hughes inc oneconnect from
红宝石休斯公司的交易来自
walls of the often unsatisfied postage provides great support live trading with
经常不满意的邮资墙为实时交易提供了极大的支持
multiple for breaking dawn of the
打破黎明的倍数
universe is a group of weight watchers
宇宙是一群体重观察者
and promote
并促进
die office leon i want to consider the study of data
利昂去办公室我想考虑数据研究
that means the strategy with people and the pacific shop set of the remains
这意味着与人和太平洋遗迹店的战略
of forensic services and text stocks europe filter sound text whether your flyer
法医服务和文本库欧洲过滤声音文本是否为您的传单
lined expensive security suite office security which is the alpha model
内衬昂贵的安全套件办公室安全，它是Alpha模型
Williams Interplay Assist was apprehended by 1 Alpha School Securitys
Williams Interplay Assist被1个Alpha School Securitys逮捕
the university motto des alfa scholes represents director social networks
阿尔法·斯考尔斯大学座右铭代表总监社交网络
level of confidence generated in the display is not track day trader tradesignal
显示中生成的置信度不是跟踪日交易者的交易信号
communication and recommendations for
沟通和建议
traders from model a turning to change the portfolio in other words des sv
交易者从模型转向改变投资组合换句话说des sv
estedt hermanns capital se located signals according to which the isis
埃斯特德·赫尔曼斯资本公司根据信号位置确定信号
portfolio construction models is an equal weighted model of the same art of
投资组合建设模型是具有同等价值的等值加权模型。
hair tattoos position but for the dance you might want more specifically the door
头发纹身的位置，但对于舞蹈，您可能想要更具体的门
high level of conference about shoe fashion basking sharks this is the pension
关于鞋类时尚鲨鱼的高层会议，这是退休金
implementation on the motto next up is the transaction cost motto until 9 pm action
接下来的座右铭实施是直到晚上9点为止的交易成本座右铭
Kost sondheims to motto of integrated into the execution portfolio construction
科斯特·桑德海姆（Kost Sondheims）的座右铭是融入执行组合建设
the motto huge des model is important is the song time since the world to
座右铭巨大的des模型很重要，是自世界以来的歌曲时间
hide fans action kost expect to make money to cover the transaction costs
隐藏粉丝行动科斯特期望赚钱来支付交易费用
motto position that means with office transaction
座右铭意味着与办公室交易
cautious trade commission sec transaction cost model of the mails or
谨慎的交易佣金或邮件交易成本模型
the cost such lippitsch a market impact cost
这样的利器成本，对市场的影响成本
The pending home sales and trade william does not have a significant impact on the bottom
待定的房屋销售和贸易意愿不会对底部产生重大影响
line with this very important to consider
符合这个非常重要的考虑
your motto the sponsor for standing from the chat trading that is the execution
您的座右铭是发起人在聊天交易中立于不败之地的赞助商
model of the motto of the hessian will be opened des tals und harmonie trade order
粗麻布座右铭的模型将被开放，以期建立和谐的贸易秩序。
to business b to what can of traders only when the soldiers and out and more
到商号b到什么时候才能有交易员，只有当士兵出入等等
especially for bio des caddy very important display top trade in for
特别是对于bio des caddy来说，非常重要的显示顶级交易
inter multiple smallest apps for the teninger importance of the trade centers
为贸易中心的Teninger重要性提供多个最小的应用程序
limit orders market order to last but not least the batteries is the motto
限价订单市场订单持续但并非最不重要的是电池座右铭
part of the trading algorithms the monitoring portfolios risk manager
交易算法的一部分，监控投资组合风险管理器
position 2 ssrs simple example of his model and how to get this position it is
位置2 ssrs他的模型的简单示例，以及如何获得该位置
one thing seldom presented and whether the muslim strength of the model can
很少介绍一件事，以及该模型的穆斯林力量是否可以
you watch at complex not that into the jelly roll into the paint and very much
您会看到复杂的东西，而不是进入果冻，卷入油漆，而且非常
of and des models of very important than
的和des的模型比
what and words and using it for any trading universe lesson motto only ones
什么和单词，并将其用于任何交易世界课程座右铭
to trade liquidity us financial stores das white or us financial stoxx bad
交易流动性，美国金融商店达斯怀特或美国金融斯托克不好
day the dollar volume's thickest top ten hits trading universe of the alpha
美元交易量最厚的前十天触及阿尔法的交易空间
model at comeback the cool trading price on the stents doctor of fifty
卷土重来的模型在五十多岁的支架医生上很酷的交易价格
daily leverage effect of the fifth third cell signer
第五个第三单元格签名者的每日杠杆效应
the secondos agent picked up the portfolio construction model and creates
secondos代理选择投资组合构建模型并创建
the station position segways conveyor maxx or todtmoos 1 75 percent on the
站位segways输送机maxx或todtmoos 1 75％
world map of the alu kate attraction kosmos very simple 15 display trade commission
阿卢·凯特景点世界地图非常简单的15个显示贸易委员会
simply discuss the cost of sleep and market impact
只需讨论睡眠成本和市场影响
disneys the transaction cost model the model jenny trades has the door already
迪士尼交易成本模型詹妮交易的模型已经有了门。
saxon costs he is model toni maniac of the endgame position profit
撒克逊人花费他是终端游戏头寸利润的典型托尼狂人
of the century physical solution model to present tourism development last but
提出旅游业发展的世纪物理解决方案模型
not least execution model is cool ones we come on get nm
尤其重要的是执行模型很酷，我们来得到nm
because open source it is great with brand depending on information aggressive from
因为开放源代码对品牌很有帮助，这取决于来自以下方面的积极信息
Model job torn from the portfolio construction from the letter traffic light gives the answer
从字母红绿灯的投资组合构造中撕下的模型工作给出了答案
this time so that no luck is on track that is very simple example in
这次，这样就不会碰运气了，这是一个非常简单的例子
reality this time the child is incredibly complex depending on the strategy and
这次的现实情况是，根据策略和策略，孩子变得异常复杂
implementation because in the beginning the best start ups implant are now continuing
实施，因为一开始最好的启动植入程序现在正在继续
from the name of the framework trading algorithm video nietzsche service &amp;
从框架交易算法视频nietzsche服务的名称和
trading implement trading algorithms in python sketch instead of the ground
交易在python草图而不是地面中实现交易算法
connect platform in the new video this makes the video below the threshold of 3
在新视频中连接平台，这使得视频低于3的阈值
Reveal the notification belfort content was watching tanks before
揭露belfort内容是在看坦克之前的通知